Planned Parenthood Federation of America Records (PPFA II): SERIES II. CLASSIFIED FILES, 1921-80 (Part 1)
Sophia Smith Collection
- SERIES II. CLASSIFIED FILES (part 1)
  - Field Department
    - Regional Workshops Calendar
      - 1971-74 (Box 57, Folder 73)
      - 1976 (Box 57)
    - Suggested Guidelines for Standards of Affiliation for Chapters Within State Organizations 1969-70 (Box 57, Folder 74)
    - Summer Apprenticeship Program for Medical Students, 1971 (Box 57, Folder 75)
    - SURVEYS
      - Surveys, General Correspondence, 1970-73 (Box 57, Folder 76)
      - Summary of Data Received on Recruitment, Use, Training of Auxiliary Personnel in PP Programs, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 77)
      - Survey of Man Days Required for the Certification of an Affiliate, 1973 (Box 57, Folder 78)
      - Survey of Non-Contraceptive Clinic Service, 1970 (Box 57, Folder 79)
      - Survey of PP-WP Staff Visits in Wisconsin, 1971 (Box 57, Folder 80)
      - Special Services Survey, 1973 (Box 57, Folder 81)
      - Task Force on Standardization of Delivery of Services & Clinical Management, 1977 (Box 57, Folder 82)
    - STAFF
      - Allen, Gerald, Correspondence & Memos, 1976-77 (Box 58, Folder 1)
      - Bernheim, Doris
        - Field Staff, Correspondence & Memos, 1969-74 (Box 58, Folder 2-4)
        - Revised Version of Regional Office Procedures, 1972 (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - Berzire, Richard, Staff
      - Gale Largey's Proposal, 1970 (Box 58, Folder 6)
      - Correspondence & Memos, 1970 (Box 58, Folder 7)
      - Chronological, 1970 (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - Cowles, Wylda, Field Staff, Quarterly Report, Biographical Material, 1962 (Box 58, Folder 9)
    - Edwards, Willie
      - Correspondence and Memos
        - 1973-74 (Box 58, Folder 10)
        - 1975 (Box 58)
      - Participants in Affiliate Accounting Workshops, 1974 (Box 58, Folder 11)
      - Chronological, Do Not Remove Contents, 1973-74 (Box 58, Folder 12)
    - National
      - Fleishman, Norman, Personnel, Correspondence & General Field Department Report, 1966-67 (Box 58, Folder 13)
    - Gray, Naomi T.
      - Personal, Personnel Congratulatory Messages, 1960-68 (Box 58, Folder 14)
      - Personnel
        - Departmental Reports, 1957-64 (Box 58, Folder 15)
        - Memos, Interoffice, 1955-69 (Box 58, Folder 16)
        - Personal, 1955-68 (Box 58, Folder 17)
      - Field Department
        - Relationship of National to Local Organizational, 1968-69 (Box 58, Folder 18)
        - Reports, 1964-68 (Box 58, Folder 19)
    - Hyacinthe, Laurent
      - Accounting Consultant
        - 1973-74 (Box 58, Folder 20)
        - 1975 (Box 58)
      - Memos, 1975 (Box 58, Folder 21)
  - AFFILIATION SERVICES (FORMERLY FIELD SERVICE)
    - KLAPPER, JERIM
      - ACCOUNTS RECEIVED SAMUEL FILD, ESQ
        - Administrative Manual, 1973 (Box 58, Folder 22)
        - Central Office Manual, 1973 (Box 58, Folder 23)
    - Lee, Dorothea
      - Affiliate Services
        - Activity Report Training Program, 1977 (Box 58, Folder 24)
        - Affiliate Audits, Delinquent & Problem, 1975-78 (Box 58, Folder 25)
        - Alternatives Regional Restructuring, 1977 (Box 58, Folder 26)
      - Field Department
        - Comments on Field Department Plan, 1974 (Box 58, Folder 27)
        - Correspondence & Memos, 1976-78 (Box 58, Folder 28)
      - Field Staff, Correspondence & Memos
        - 1972-74 (Box 58, Folder 29)
        - 1975 (Box 58)
      - Draft Procedures for Recertification, 1977 (Box 58, Folder 30)
      - Field Department
        - Draft Format Regional Office Plans, 1976 (Box 58, Folder 31)
        - Field Visit Reports, 1977 (Box 58, Folder 32)
        - Model Formats Affiliate Planning, 1974 (Box 58, Folder 33)
        - NEDC Personnel Survey, 1973 (Box 58, Folder 34)
        - Procedures for Site Visit, 1976 (Box 58, Folder 35)
        - Replies to Memo, Expectations, Small, Large Affiliates, Field Directors, 1974 (Box 58, Folder 36)
        - Field Reports, 1972 (Box 58, Folder 37)
        - Summary of Activities, 1976-77 (Box 58, Folder 38)
        - Viability of Educational Affiliates, 1973 (Box 58, Folder 39)
      - Chronological
        - 1972-74 (Box 58, Folder 40)
        - 1975-78 (Box 58)
  - Series II, Due to it's large size, the SERIES II container list is divided into two parts. Go to Part 2.